You're done now.
Those who control auto-tracking Stands…
It's F.F.!
Why are they at this Disciplinary Wing?
He has a disc!
Pale Snake is nearby!
Where is he?
No way…
The one who threw it was…
It can't be him!
So the one who controls Pale Snake is…
You are…
Father Pucchi.
F.F. feared one thing above all else.
It wasn't the destruction of their body,
but the elimination
of their own intellect.
I remember everything
since the day I met Jolyne.
The weird graffiti on prison phones,
the lint-covered blankets on the bed,
and the smell of garbage.
The guard's shouts,
the sounds of doors opening and closing,
and the toilet flushing, even.
Fooling around with Jolyne
and the others and laughing together.
I remember them all.
But before I met Jolyne at the farm,
though I lived there for years,
all I can recall from that time are
memories that are like a machine's.
That's all.
I followed orders
without ever questioning why
and spent the days
guarding Pale Snake's discs.
But now, I know
that to live means to make memories.
I fear losing them the most.
Jolyne is on a mission to save her father
and is willing to risk her life
for the ones she cares about like Ermes.
That's probably because
she has good memories of them.
That's what powers humans up.
Memories give humans
power to keep going at a cellular level.
This is an understanding that I,
F.F., lacked before meeting Jolyne.
That's right.
That is…
That is what it means
to be an intelligent being.
Which do you prioritize?
Is it me?
Or is it finishing D an' G?
You hesitated for a split second!
That will cost you your life!
I gave you intellect and a Stand.
I am taking it back.
When I think about Jolyne,
I feel courage swelling up inside me.
This is what memories do.
This is… my intellect!
What?
No…
Is F.F. planning to--
Their bodily fluids entered his body!
Impossible…
Am I…
Looks like F.F. did it.
They must have killed its User.
Where is the fruit?
What the hell?
Does this mean that it's born?
Is this what Pale Snake wanted?
What the hell is this thing?
Why was it given life?
Why does it exist here?
Were the prisoners mutated
just to give life to this thing?
Now that it's born,
my body is no longer mutating.
It stopped turning into a plant.
You must not let F.F. escape!
Read the memory inside the disc!
Tell me the whereabouts
of the spawn of Dio's bone!
Will I even last 30 seconds
when I'm exposed like this?
I need water.
I need to tell Jolyne
who Pale Snake really is!
Shit.
I have to tell her that
he's the prison's chaplain, Father Pucchi!
Are you trying to reach the
faucet at the entrance?
Before you go,
I have one question for you!
You can't escape my Stand!
There's one thing I want to ask, F.F.
It's a very simple question.
Did you see it?
Did you see the thing born
at the Disciplinary Wing?
How did it look?
Was it a plant?
Was it beautiful?
What is a priest doing
at a prison like this?
I hope you understand that
I'm asking the questions here.
I can easily extract your memory
and read it to understand what was born.
But I wanted to know how you felt.
Things like it looked soft
or that it was beautiful
are your opinions, and can't be read
from a memory disc.
Are you worried that the spawn
will escape?
You're afraid of losing it.
Is it able to move already?
How the hell should I know?
I'd be more worried about it
getting destroyed.
No, maybe it's already done.
Jolyne is with that mean asshole,
after all.
If she's compelled to,
she'll finish it off.
It's impossible to defeat it.
That will never happen.
No one can destroy it,
that much I know well.
My only concern is Jolyne
causing trouble and losing it.
Jotaro's memory alone is enough
to control the birthed creature,
and I have his memory.
We are so close to the end.
What is it shaped like?
Did it grow faster than you expected?
I thought it was gonna drown in water.
And then, what else was there?
Let's see…
It's stalling for time! Turn around!
I did it!
My soul isn't in my head,
it's over there.
I have water now!
I can go tell Jolyne everything!
Your soul, you say?
No matter where your intelligence lies,
you're not the one making decisions here.
I am the one who endowed you
with a Stand ability.
You filthy plankton!
Don't you dare give me explanations,
as if you know better than I do!
My body! This water…
What is streaming out of it?
No, it can't be!
It's steaming hot water.
No aquatic organism on earth can dwell
in water hotter than 32 degrees Celsius.
A different Stand ability that
turns water into hot water…
…was inserted into this thing.
Only I get to decide
where your intellect lies.
You are using your own ability to turn
the water you touch
into boiling hot water!
Jolyne!
STAND NAME: GREEN, GREEN, GREEN HOME
STAND MASTER: THE GREEN BABY
Where is it? Where did it fall?
Shit, don't tell me it drowned.
No…
Does it have a mind of its own?
Since it's trying to escape?
No…
Instinct is its only drive.
I don't know whether it's a plant or not,
but I don't want it to go anywhere.
I can't let Pale Snake have it.
Jolyne!
Wait, Jolyne!
Don't move, look at the rock by your foot!
Listen closely.
Don't take another step.
Turn around and look at me.
When the pebble rolled over here,
it turned into a rock.
Meanwhile, Jolyne, you grew smaller.
Stop! I said don't go near it!
What just happened, Anastasia?
Why did you grow shorter?
- What's going on, Anastasia?
- Stay calm, Jolyne.
By the way, how big
does that baby look to you?
It hasn't changed.
Its size is the same as before.
Anastasia,
it looks like you are the one
who grew shorter to me.
What's going on?
The baby's size looks
about average to me too.
Only the pebble
we kicked over got smaller.
Jolyne, don't move.
Stay right where you are.
You're back to normal.
Do you think that
this is the baby's ability?
The closer we get to the baby,
the shorter we grow.
I don't have a clue.
That's a heavy line of questioning.
Now listen, if we get halfway to the baby,
my height shrinks by half.
That means we have to walk twice as much.
Okay.
Furthermore, if we get
a fourth of the way to the baby,
then the distance grows by four times.
At one-eighth,
we walk eight times as much.
1/32nd,
1/64th,
1/128th…
Our body will keep shrinking,
while the distance
multiplies more and more.
Here is the question.
Will we ever reach that baby?
I say no, not in an eternity.
But in order to get
my father's memory back,
I have to get the baby.
- Jolyne.
- Anastasia, we'll think
after we've done everything we can!
It's her focus.
The way Jolyne can fixate
towards one goal.
I'm here because I'm drawn to
the way she focuses on one thing.
The ability to concentrate
enhances a person's beauty.
Those eyes…
In time, I'll have you gaze at me
with that intense focus of yours.
Stone Ocean!
I'm about to reach it! I can catch it!
It's no use, Jolyne.
Pull your thread back!
There is no way to reach the baby!
I can't give up!
There has to be an end.
I mean, it's right there!
What do you say to jumping off from here?
If I do, I'll reach an end point.
The ground is the finishing point.
I have to land at some point!
Stop, Jolyne! Don't--
Yes! The ground is right there!
I can almost reach it!
What's happening?
My string…
What the hell is that?
Don't tell me…
Is this the baby's Stand?
Damn, haven't I reached the ground yet?
It hasn't only grown in size,
but in power as well!
Its power has multiplied!
This Stand… It appeared
just to drag me down,
so I won't ever escape
this never-ending fall!
Stone Ocean!
If this is the baby's ability,
then catching the Stand
is the same as catching the User!
I'm shrinking!
It's trying to reduce me to nothing!
The end I thought I'd reach
wasn't the ground.
It was this Stand!
Diver Drive.
The closer you get to the baby,
the smaller you get.
Eventually, you will be
reduced to nothing.
I don't know why a baby
with such a powerful Stand was born,
but I know he will be an enemy someday.
Jolyne, this baby is your enemy.
But…
if there's no way to defeat it,
then I really can't let
Pale Snake have it.
Anastasia, hold on tight!
It threw the rock!
Does that mean…
that it's thinking for itself?
The baby is now
deliberately using its ability!
It's coming. Climb!
We need to escape as fast as possible!
Run!
No matter how much we chase it,
we will never reach that baby.
But at least, we caught the Stand.
Jolyne, do you still not see
what we were climbing toward?
It was a gamble.
The baby is intelligent and curious.
Earlier, it touched the bottle I threw.
When the baby chooses to touch an object,
its size stays the same.
In other words,
the bottle's size hasn't changed.
If we can't catch the baby,
we'll have the baby chase after us.
We finally reached the bottle.
The Stand is inside the bottle now.
All we have to do now
is trap it inside the bottle!
But… how are we getting out of here?
I'm having Diver Drive enter
the bottle's wall.
It's bringing the mouth to us.
Let's go, Jolyne.
Run for it!
We finally caught it.
We got its User, the baby too.
It's changing its position.
It's using the bottle to charge forward!
Anastasia!
Stone Ocean!
Jolyne!
You can't break the bottle.
We'll be worse off
if we have to face the Stand!
Did the baby have this in mind
when it rolled the bottle?
Shit, we're in deep trouble now!
- Don't break the bottle!
- But…
At this rate, you're done for!
Anastasia, look…
What the hell?
What's going on?
Jolyne, looks like…
it's interested in the star-shaped
birthmark on your left shoulder.
Since it touched you,
we turned back to our original size.
The baby has the same birthmark
on its shoulder.
What's going on?
The baby acts like it has known
Jolyne for a long time.
Hey, it looks as if it likes me.
What should I do?
It likes her? No, that's not it.
I have no doubt about it.
He will turn against us.
I can only sense endless darkness
from this baby's ability.
Yes, we may need this baby
to retrieve your father's disc
from Pale Snake,
but I must kill it while I can.
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter